aoamedia.com 2013-03-09

# AOAMEDIA.COM PRIVACY STATEMENT

AOAMEDIA.COM PRIVACY STATEMENT

* * *

AoAMedia.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following statement to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the AoAMedia.com Web site. The AoAMedia.com web site is owned and operated by AoAMedia.com.

Collection of your personal information 

When AoAMedia.com collects any personal information on our corporate website, we will express our need for the personal data at the point of collection. Some of the reasons why we collect your personal information include: 

  * registration to A o A Media products
  * provide registered users a more personalized and meaningful experience on the AoA Media website.   

Uses of your personal information:

We will only use your personal information in the way we specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way your personal information is used without your consent. Some of the ways we may use your personal information include: 

  * To provide the ability to contact you, and provide you with software update and promotion information. 
  * To provide customer feedback and support. 

Privacy of Children

AoAMedia.com does not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from or about children under 13. If we discover that we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. 

As Required By Law

AoA Media. com may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on A o A M e d i a.com or to protect and defend the rights or property of AoAMedia.com. 

Security

Ao A Media uses administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard personal identifying information against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. However, as effective as these measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.
